popularsuperstars.com 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy -

**Disclaimer**

The Popular Superstars site zeroes in on the less visible (but spicier and intriguing) aspects of the lives and lifestyles of popular personalities today—in showbiz, business, industry or politics. We rummage through the Net to get the latest updates on popular public figures that make it to superstardom and bring you all the spicy tidbits—all the noteworthy details.

And we choose only online sources with insider scoops to derive our stories from.

However, we do not guarantee that all the information we get from our sources are accurate. We have no control over their news reportage and how they present it online. Any inaccuracy or outright wrong information found on Popular Superstars, therefore, is not intentional and not designed to malign anyone and cannot be the responsibility, in any way, of this site. Moreover, the site’s admin, managers and writers cannot be held responsible in any way in this regard.

Rest assured, however, that the site and the people involved in it are doing their best to bring you quality news and article items.

 **Privacy Policy**

Be informed that the Popular Superstars site uses an application to collect personal data from its visitors and users. Here are the kinds of data collected:

  1. Data derived through cookies

Third parties connected through links on this site may also collect users’ personal data once they visit those third party sites via the links, but Popular Superstars is not responsible for such data collection. Users are therefore advised to read the privacy policies of said sites before using them.

This site may have users freely provide their personal data, but at other times it may simply automatically collect the same upon visitors’ use of this site. Cookies and other tracking tools used on this site are primarily for identifying users only and specifically to remember their preferences and provide them with fast and convenient service. Without the personal data, this site may find it impossible to render its services to visitors and users.

Users will also be held responsible for the personal data of third parties shared, obtained or published through this site’s application, practically confirming that they have the third party’s approval to provide such data to this site.

 **Other Uses for Personal Data**

Aside from using the personal data for rendering site services to users, they will also be used for ads and promos, external social network links, analytics, behavioral targeting, contacting users, managing contacts and sending them messages, and for traffic optimization.

The use and collection of information by third-party advertising service providers are governed by the relevant third party’s Privacy Notice and are not covered by our Privacy Notice. If you would like more information about the information collection practices of a particular service provider, or if you would like more information on how to opt out of a service provider’s information collection practices, go to [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). You can opt out of the use of cookies by DoubleClick, one of our service providers, by visiting [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy). Additionally, many of our advertising service providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). You can obtain more information about these advertising service providers’ information collection practices, and opt out of such practices (and at the same time opt out of the collection practices of other, or all, NAI members) by following the opt out instructions on the NAI’s website at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).If you would like more information on how to opt out of information collection practices, go to [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).
